{
    "subject": "resource/Marie-Magdeleine",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Oratorio",
    "human_readable": "Marie-Magdeleine is an Oratorio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6167569756507874,
            "question": "What type of structure is Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3567492365837097,
            "question": "Can you name a specific Oratorio that is well-known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3556191027164459,
            "question": "Where might you find an Oratorio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28941813111305237,
            "question": "What is the primary purpose of an Oratorio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2454090714454651,
            "question": "Give an example of a musical performance that might take place in an Oratorio."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21412742137908936,
            "question": "How does an Oratorio differ from a concert hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1881445199251175,
            "question": "What role does an audience typically play in an Oratorio performance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1665714830160141,
            "question": "Are there any famous composers associated with Oratorios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.026201466098427773,
            "question": "What architectural features are commonly found in Oratories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0189812071621418,
            "question": "What historical period saw the rise of Oratories?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marie-Magdeleine is an Oratorio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What architectural features are commonly found in Oratories?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous composers associated with Oratorios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role does an audience typically play in an Oratorio performance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2546_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2546/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt mentions that Massenet's oratorio Marie-Magdeleine had a great impression on Tchaikovsky, and this led to Tchaikovsky composing a Romance for his Seven Romances, Op. 47. This suggests that Marie-Magdeleine is indeed an Oratorio."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"Marie Magdeleine Oratorio Drame Sacr\u00e9 en 3 Actes & 4 Parties\" and describe it as a work by Jules Massenet, confirming that Marie-Magdeleine is indeed an oratorio."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}